## ROSHANAK GHADIRY

# GRAPHIC DESIGN PROFESSIONAL

- in linkedin.com/in/roshanakghadiry
- roshan@floralgraphix.com
- www.floralgraphix.com

## **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

Photoshop
Illustrator
Indesign
HTML5/CSS3
Javascript
JQuary
Joomla /CMS
Wordpress
PHP MySQL
Acrobat
Powerpoint
Photography



## **OBJECTIVE**

Creative Graphic Designer (print and web) with over 15 years experience developing strong visual concepts and signature branding for top corporations in both Canada and the US. Motivated professional with excellent interpersonal skills who drives corporate success by providing sound technical and design support. Known for working well with sales, marketing and other relevant departments to support efforts through design of high-quality key visual materials.

#### **KEY SKILLS**

- » Rigorous attention to detail
- » Creative and agile thinker who is self-motivated and collaborative
- » Ability to multitask and manage project priorities to meet deadlines, without compromising quality
- » Team player with a strong track record of driving performance improvements
- » Ability to thrive in a fast-paced, deadline-driven environment

## **EMPLOYMENT**

## GRAPHIC DESIGNER

MISSISSAUGA 2014-2019

## GRAPHIC DESIGNER

US & CANADA 2013-2019

## GRAPHIC & WEB SPECIALIST

TORONTO 2011-2013

## GRAPHIC & WEB SPECIALIST

TORONTO 2005-2011

#### PROPHIX SOFTWARE

Created visual communications through the use of graphics, typography, photography, and illustration. Updated existing graphics that may include print, digital, social media, signage and other graphics or templates. (www.prophix.com)

#### THE ASCII GROUP

Designed and executed original marketing collateral, including print, digital media, advertising, web and more. (www.ascii.com); (www.asciievents.com)

### LEVEL PLATFORMS (AVAST AVG TECH.)

Contributed expertise to all aspects of the marketing process from design conception to web analytics, leveraging hybrid web and print design skillset, leading to the acquisition of this Canadian company to a European firm.(www.levelplatforms.com)

#### **PCI GEOMATICS**

Designed, updated and maintained external, internal corporate and reseller websites. Designed all kinds of graphics for various tradeshows and in-house events. (www.pcigeomatics.com)

## ROSHANAK GHADIRY

# GRAPHIC DESIGN PROFESSIONAL

- in linkedin.com/in/roshanakghadiry
- roshan@floralgraphix.com
- www.floralgraphix.com

### **AWARDS**

Marketing Excellent Award, Mississauga, ON,

2016

Employee Recognition Award, PCI Geomatics, Toronto, ON 2006



## **EDUCATION**

### **ADOBE**

TORONTO 2005-2007

## **SENECA**

TORONTO 2004-2005

## **GEORGE BROWN**

TORONTO 2001-2002

### ADOBE CERTIFIED EXPERT(PRINT & WEB)

Official Exams include Adobe Photoshop, Adobe InDesign, Adobe Acrobat Professional Print Production, and Macromedia Dreamweaver-

### DIGITAL MEDIA ARTS DIPLOMA

focus on the design, implementation and management of digital graphics, animation, video and audio for interactive multimedia applications, including applications for the Internet.Completed with honors.

#### **DESKTOP PUBLISHING CERTIFICATE**

Focus on foundation in design principles as well as training in the main software applications used within the industry.

## **TESTIMONIALS**

## MARKETING MANAGER

LEVELPLATFORMS 2011-2013

#### **ED GOFFIN**

As a manager, I could always count on Roshanak to meet deadlines, deliver exemplary customer service to internal and external customers, and provide insight and suggestions on how to improve processes and programs. She is hardworking, dedicated and a pleasure to work with – all the things you want in a coworker and employee ... ##

https://www.linkedin.com/in/roshanakghadiry

## MARKETING MANAGER

LEVEL PLATFORMS PCI GEOMATICS 2006-2013

### **ALYSIA VETTER**

Roshanak's skill set is an amazing hybrid of web and print design. She understands full circle the marketing process from design conception to web analytics and is eager to participate in projects that challenge her creatively and provide the best ROI ... 
https://www.linkedin.com/in/roshanakghadiry

# GLOBAL CHANNEL MANAGER

PCI GEOMATICS 2010-2011

#### **ANNE SKINNER**

Many times, we were under tight deadlines and pressure. Roshanak always maintained her composure and provided guidance to the team to enable us to meet goals and objectives on time ... It https://www.linkedin.com/in/roshanakghadiry